Shed Garvey, the medical tech, was hunched over his lab table.;{'entities': [(0, 11, 'PERSON')]}
Shed's been tellin' me about how the prosthetic is gonna hook up to it.;{'entities': [(0, 4, 'PERSON')]}
Dresden is a piece of shit.;{'entities': [(0, 7, 'PERSON')]}
“There's some infection,” Shed said.;{'entities': [(26, 30, 'PERSON')]}
The one called Mole.;{'entities': [(15, 19, 'PERSON')]}
The fire spraying across Dookie's body.;{'entities': [(25, 31, 'PERSON')]}
Hasini caught Miller's eyes.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (14, 20, 'PERSON')]}
Holden let the comment hang in the air for a second while Shed's ears turned crimson.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (58, 62, 'PERSON')]}
Shaddid and Ramachandra and all the rest of them should think better of me.;{'entities': [(0, 7, 'PERSON'), (12, 23, 'PERSON')]}
The company shed 100 jobs.;{}
She shed some tears.;{}
Roger that El Tee.;{}
Trouble El Tee?;{}
What's going on El Tee?;{}
Roger that.;{}
Solid copy on that.;{}
Copy that.;{}
A thin foil of Mylar.;{}
The Mylar faceplate had cracked.;{}
Detainment was a bad scenario.;{}
Detainment by the inner planet navies was a bad scenario.;{}
Deck after deck.;{}
Fuck their magic McGuffin.;{}
Ladar and radar are instruments on a spaceship.;{}
Radar and ladar are instruments on a spaceship.;{}
Ladar says it's a big hole in the side.;{}
Radar says that they are still five klicks out.;{'entities': [(31, 42, 'QUANTITY')]}
The monitor showed a massive IR spike.;{}
This is a pre-Epstein drive.;{}
The Coriolis effect made him a little unsteady.;{}
The ship was equipped with an Epstein Drive.;{}
The MCRN Sally Ride had three decks: the bridge, CIC, and engineering.;{'entities': [(9, 19, 'SHIP')]}
Taking a ship's CIC is important in QCB.;{}
She'll do fine for fifty thousand klicks in vacuum.;{'entities': [(19, 40, 'QUANTITY')]}
They stopped about two million klicks out.;{'entities': [(19, 37, 'QUANTITY')]}
Eros jumped two hundred klicks spinward.;{'entities': [(0, 4, 'LOC'), (12, 30, 'QUANTITY')]}
The torpedoes are now at over forty klicks a second and accelerating.;{'entities': [(30, 42, 'QUANTITY')]}
Malthus Tycho was an engineering genius.;{'entities': [(0, 13, 'PERSON')]}
Havelock turned in the cart while Miller went to his cubicle.;{'entities': [(0, 8, 'PERSON'), (34, 40, 'PERSON')]}
Naomi here's been signed on for ages.;{'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON')]}
Make sure Shed does heal fast.;{'entities': [(10, 14, 'PERSON')]}
Captain Shaddid looked pained.;{'entities': [(0, 15, 'PERSON')]}
A blue that Havelock assured him matched the Earth's summer sky.;{'entities': [(12, 20, 'PERSON'), (45, 50, 'LOC')]}
The old west affectation common to everyone from the Mariner Valley annoyed Holden.;{'entities': [(53, 67, 'LOC'), (76, 82, 'PERSON')]}
If you had an impossible engineering job that needed to be done in the Belt, you hired Tycho.;{'entities': [(71, 75, 'LOC'), (87, 92, 'ORG')]}
You'll still have the Ceres assignments you have now.;{'entities': [(22, 27, 'LOC')]}
In the Ceres spin gravity.;{'entities': [(7, 12, 'LOC')]}
Holden thinks often of Ade Tukunbo.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (23, 34, 'PERSON')]}
Titania is a moon in the solar system.;{'entities': [(0, 7, 'LOC'),(25, 37, 'LOC')]}
Spinning it up to 0.3 g had taken the best minds at Tycho Manufacturing half a generation;{'entities': [(18, 23, 'QUANTITY'), (52, 71, 'ORG')]}
Holden was floating in zero g.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (23, 29, 'QUANTITY')]}
The thrust dropped to a tolerable half a g.;{'entities': [(34, 42, 'QUANTITY')]}
Javier Liu, was a structural engineer from Tycho.;{'entities': [(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (43, 48, 'ORG')]}
It's the site of a big construction project Tycho is working on.;{'entities': [(44, 49, 'ORG')]}
Tycho Manufacturing and Engineering Concern was one of the first major corporations to move into the Belt.;{'entities': [(0, 43, 'ORG')]}
In the early days of expansion, Tycho engineers and a fleet of ships had captured a small comet.;{'entities': [(32, 37, 'ORG')]}
As an encore, Tycho had built the massive reaction drives into the rock of Ceres and Eros.;{'entities': [(14, 19, 'ORG'), (75, 80, 'LOC'), (85, 89, 'LOC')]}
Went off to college, got involved with a group called the Far Horizons Foundation.;{'entities': [(58, 81, 'ORG')]}
He wondered which side Captain Shaddid would be on if the OPA attacked.;{'entities': [(23, 38, 'PERSON'), (58, 61, 'NORP')]}
Fuck the Inners;{'entities': [(9, 15, 'NORP')]}
Inners don't understand Belters;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'NORP'), (24, 31, 'NORP')]}
Holden is a lowly Earther.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (18, 25, 'NORP')]}
Alex is a cool Martian.;{'entities': [(0, 4, 'PERSON'), (15, 22, 'NORP')]}
Naomi is a tough Belter.;{'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON'), (17, 23, 'NORP')]}
This is Belter quality.;{'entities': [(8, 14, 'NORP')]}
A veteran of Thoth Station.;{'entities': [(13, 26, 'LOC')]}
On any given day, a thousand ships might be docked on Ceres Station.;{'entities': [(54, 67, 'LOC')]}
It was apparently deeply meaningful in the youth culture of Tycho Station.;{'entities': [(60, 73, 'LOC')]}
His Belter bones were longer than those of Earthers or Martians.;{'entities': [(4, 10, 'NORP'), (43, 51, 'NORP'), (55, 63, 'NORP')]}
Amos loves the Belt.;{'entities': [(0, 4, 'PERSON'), (15, 19, 'LOC')]}
Detective Miller worked for Star Helix Security.;{'entities': [(0, 16, 'PERSON'), (28, 47, 'ORG')]}
Star Helix was an Earth corporation.;{'entities': [(0, 10, 'ORG'), (18, 23, 'LOC')]}
Star Helix is responsible for Ceres security.;{'entities': [(0, 10, 'ORG'), (30, 35, 'LOC')]}
Collecting protection money for the Golden Bough Society.;{'entities': [(36, 56, 'ORG')]}
Golden Bough's looking the same as Sohiro's crew and the Loca Greiga.;{'entities': [(0, 12, 'ORG'), (35, 41, 'ORG'), (57, 68, 'ORG')]}
You're telling me the Loca Greiga stopped charging protection?;{'entities': [(22, 33, 'ORG')]}
So why hasn't the Golden Bough meted out some gangster justice?;{'entities': [(18, 30, 'ORG')]}
The OPA was beloved by the people it helped;{'entities': [(4, 7, 'NORP')]}
Opa was beloved by the people he helped.;{'entities': [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]}
Meaning Star Helix Security has accepted a contract for services separate from the Ceres security assignment.;{'entities': [(8, 27, 'ORG'), (83, 88, 'LOC')]}
The Earth-Mars Coalition Navy often passed through Ceres on its way to Saturn;{'entities': [(4, 29, 'ORG'), (51, 56, 'LOC'), (71, 77, 'LOC')]}
Last records show she was employed on Tycho LOC.;{'entities': [(38, 51, 'LOC')]}
I know she shipped out for Tycho.;{'entities': [(27, 32, 'LOC')]}
Tycho was a city, and he suddenly felt very much like a foreigner.;{'entities': [(0, 5, 'LOC')]}
Why was a gas hauler going between Pallas and Tycho?;{'entities': [(35, 41, 'LOC'), (46, 51, 'LOC')]}
Anyone who doesn't live on a spaceship is structurally vulnerable. Tycho, Eros, Pallas, Ceres.;{'entities': [(67, 72, 'LOC'), (74, 78, 'LOC'), (80, 86, 'LOC'), (88, 93, 'LOC')]}
Tycho LOC was the headquarters of Tycho in the Belt.;{'entities': [(0, 13, 'LOC'), (38, 43, 'LOC'), (51, 55, 'LOC')]}
Making Tycho LOC the largest mobile construction platform in the solar system.;{'entities': [(7, 20, 'LOC'), (69, 81, 'LOC')]}
People aren't just going to forget about ships, like the Donnager.;{'entities': [(57, 65, 'SHIP')]}
The Scopuli had been taken eight days ago, and Julie Mao was finally ready to be shot.;{'entities': [(4, 11, 'SHIP'), (47, 56, 'PERSON')]}
The few sensor logs that still streamed showed no sign of the Scopuli.;{'entities': [(62, 69, 'SHIP')]}
Light freighter. Martian registry. Shows Eros as home port. Calls itself Scopuli ...;{'entities': [(17, 24, 'GPE'), (41, 45, 'LOC'), (73, 80, 'SHIP')]}
The image the Knight created by bouncing a laser off the Scopuli's hull.;{'entities': [(14, 20, 'SHIP'), (57, 64, 'SHIP')]}
Knight's landing gear isn't going to be good in atmosphere until I can get the seals replaced.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'SHIP')]}
Holden, where does the Knight stand?;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (23, 29, 'SHIP')]}
the Canterbury was a retooled colony transport;{'entities': [(4, 14, 'SHIP')]}
output of the Canterbury's reactor and engine updating in the corners;{'entities': [(14, 24, 'SHIP')]}
If the Canterbury sensed an anomaly;{'entities': [(7, 17, 'SHIP')]}
MCRN Sally Ride this is Captain James Holden of the UNN Escort Vessel Ravi.;{'entities': [(5, 15, 'SHIP'),(32, 44, 'PERSON'),(70, 74, 'SHIP')]}
The Cant's a century-old ice hauler.;{'entities': [(4, 8, 'SHIP')]}
And the big array on the Cant can spot a kid throwing rocks on Luna.;{'entities': [(25, 29, 'SHIP'), (63, 67, 'LOC')]}
The Belt had been a far horizon of tremendous mineral wealth;{'entities': [(4, 8, 'LOC')]}
until the Mormons finished their generation ship and headed for the stars;{'entities': [(10, 17, 'NORP')]}
And then there was the Belt.;{'entities': [(23, 27, 'LOC')]}
If you asked OPA recruiters, they might say there were a hundred million in the Belt.;{'entities': [(13, 16, 'NORP'), (80, 84, 'LOC')]}
So now the Canterbury and her dozens of sister ships in the Pur'n'Kleen Water Company;{'entities': [(11, 21, 'SHIP'), (60, 85, 'ORG')]}
From Saturn's generous rings to the Belt.;{'entities': [(5, 11, 'LOC'), (36, 40, 'LOC')]}
You're the XO here;{}
Hull configuration matches the registry information.;{}
Hull configuration is looking good Cap.;{}
Hull structure took some damage.;{}
Hull structure isn't the only recognition metric.;{}
CQB stands for 'close quarter combat';{}
Everyone has an Adam's apple.;{}
The Buddha statue looked good.;{}
Nitrogen, O2, Helium-3 and oxygen are atmospheric gases.;{}
Oxygen, Helium and nitrogen are atmospheric gases.;{}
Chalk another one up.;{}
Almost immediately the PDC fire stopped.;{}
The HUD in his armor flickered.;{}
Bogey one has fired!;{}
Neural regrowth hormone? Posthuman.;{}
Get an EVA pack!;{}
The PDC got it, but it was close.;{}
The Roci and bogey two flew toward each other at suicidal speeds.;{'entities': [(4, 8, 'SHIP')]}
Alex flagged the two fast movers for the PDCs.;{'entities': [(0, 4, 'PERSON')]}
The Razorback is a racing pinnace.;{'entities': [(4, 13, 'SHIP')]}
The Donnager is a destroyer.;{'entities': [(4, 12, 'SHIP')]}
The Rocinante is a frigate bomber with PDCs.;{'entities': [(4, 13, 'SHIP')]}
The Tachi is a light frigate with point defense cannons.;{'entities': [(4, 9, 'SHIP')]}
The Roci docked at Eros on time.;{'entities': [(4, 8, 'SHIP'), (19, 23, 'LOC')]}
The Knight tried to hail the Donnager.;{'entities': [(4, 10, 'SHIP'), (29, 37, 'SHIP')]}
She'd won first place in something called the Parrish/Dorn 500K.;{}
Alex climbed up to the Knight's cockpit.;{'entities': [(0, 4, 'PERSON'), (23, 29, 'SHIP')]}
Holden said, and clicked from internal comm to the link with the Canterbury's bridge.;{'entities': [(0, 6, 'PERSON'), (65, 75, 'SHIP')]}
Bomie got jumped by a bunch of thugs.;{'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON')]}
The Blue Frog was a port bar.;{'entities': [(4, 13, 'FAC')]}
Ceres Center for Jiu Jitsu is the name of a gym.;{'entities': [(0, 12, 'FAC')]}
Julie had earned her brown belt in Jiu Jitsu.;{'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON')]}
Julie was in her office on the Razorback.;{'entities': [(0, 5, 'PERSON'), (31, 40, 'SHIP')]}
Juliette Andromeda Mao is a pinnace racer.;{'entities': [(0, 22, 'PERSON')]}
The Guy Molinari fired a Gauss round at them.;{'entities': [(0, 16, 'SHIP')]}
Corporaçõ do Gato Preto is an inport-export organization;{'entities': [(0, 23, 'ORG')]}
Sergeant Pauline Trikoloski doesn't exist.;{'entities': [(0, 27, 'PERSON')]}
Gravity is a unit measured in 'g'.;{}
They fired Teflon-coated tungsten steel rounds.;{}
The Donnie went up behind us, Cap.;{'entities': [(4, 10, 'SHIP')]}
CPM took over Protogen's security contract on Eros.;{'entities': [(0, 3, 'ORG'), (14, 22, 'ORG'), (46, 50, 'LOC')]}
CPM stands for Carne Por la Machina.;{'entities': [(0, 3, 'ORG')]}
Sematimba is a security contractor on Eros.;{'entities': [(0, 9, 'PERSON'), (38, 42, 'LOC')]}
Maokwik is short for Mao-Kwikowski Mercantile.;{'entities': [(0, 7, 'ORG'), (21, 45, 'ORG')]}
